<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim's Evening Commute</title>
    <description>Smart, relaxing mix for the drive home.</description>
    <link>https://gist.github.com/2b1ef6488ea542b51a06bc0098c859b0</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 21:25:44 GMT</pubDate>
    <itunes:author>TimBot</itunes:author>
    <itunes:image href="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e4/Robot_icon.svg"/>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Radiolab] Gray's Donation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Before he was even born, Sarah and Ross Gray knew that their son Thomas wouldn’t live long. But as they let go of him, they made a decision that reverberated through a world that they never bothered to think about. Years later, after a couple of awkward phone calls, they go on a quest and manage to meet the people and places for whom Thomas’ short life was an altogether different kind of gift. We originally made this story back in 2015, but we wanted to play it again because we love that it brings a view of science that is redemptive, tender, and unexpected.
Since we first released this episode, Sarah Gray wrote a book called A Life Everlasting (https://zpr.io/GVYisRaqe9d6), it’s a memoir about Thomas that dives into the world of organ donation and medical science. She’s also written a beautiful short story about shame called The Lacemaker Fairy Tale (https://zpr.io/Li5BMtfHmf92). And, right now she’s working on a script for a movie called Raincheck.
EPISODE CREDITS:
LATERAL CUTS -
The Cathedral (https://radiolab.org/podcast/cathedral)
The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks (https://radiolab.org/podcast/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks) 
Signup for our newsletter!! It includes short essays, recommendations, and details about other ways to interact with the show. Sign up (https://radiolab.org/newsletter)!
Radiolab is supported by listeners like you. Support Radiolab by becoming a member of The Lab (https://members.radiolab.org/) today.
Follow our show on Instagram, Twitter and Facebook @radiolab, and share your thoughts with us by emailing radiolab@wnyc.org.
Leadership support for Radiolab’s science programming is provided by the Simons Foundation and the John Templeton Foundation. Foundational support for Radiolab was provided by the Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/mgln.ai/e/14/prfx.byspotify.com/e/dts.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/waaa.wnyc.org/758af4c0-a2c3-47ec-a2d8-05f41bfbde51/episodes/f9d86f2e-c86d-4b2b-92de-c6973efec724/audio/128/default.mp3?aid=rss_feed&awCollectionId=758af4c0-a2c3-47ec-a2d8-05f41bfbde51&awEpisodeId=f9d86f2e-c86d-4b2b-92de-c6973efec724&feed=EmVW7VGp" type="audio/mpeg" length="0"/>
      <guid>https://radiolab.org/podcast/5b8230b622213510e6b435fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1640</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[The Rest Is History] The Book Club: Wuthering Heights</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Why does Emily Brontë's novel, Wuthering Heights, have such an enduring romantic association? Is Heathcliff a romantic lead, or an abusive antihero? Are the characters aspirational in any way, or irredeemable?

Join Dominic Sandbrook and Tabitha Syrett as they discuss all this and more.





Email us: ⁠thebookclub@goalhanger.com⁠

Instagram: ⁠@bookclubpodhq⁠

TikTok: ⁠@thebookclubpodhq⁠

X: ⁠@bookclubpodhq⁠

YouTube: ⁠@TheBookClubPodHQ⁠



Senior Producer: Nicole Maslen

Social Producer: Harry Balden

Video Editor: James Clayden
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://pdst.fm/e/traffic.megaphone.fm/GLT1197182799.mp3?updated=1771585806" type="audio/mpeg" length="0"/>
      <guid>undefined</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1257</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend] 12 Clomp Program</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Conan talks to film preservationist Joey in Toronto about working on famous home movie collections and uncovering remarkable footage of his own grandparents.
 
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: teamcoco.com/apply
Get access to all the podcasts you love, music channels and radio shows with the SiriusXM App! Get 3 months free using this show link: https://siriusxm.com/conan.

 Hosted by Simplecast, an AdsWizz company. See pcm.adswizz.com for information about our collection and use of personal data for advertising.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://pdrl.fm/f3efd0/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/arttrk.com/p/ST44R/claritaspod.com/measure/stitcher.simplecastaudio.com/c945bd13-c7f3-4f22-95b5-4bf98e12b21f/episodes/efdb8b2a-97e9-4f17-9b67-ac8823ad6855/audio/128/default.mp3?aid=rss_feed&awCollectionId=c945bd13-c7f3-4f22-95b5-4bf98e12b21f&awEpisodeId=efdb8b2a-97e9-4f17-9b67-ac8823ad6855&feed=dHoohVNH" type="audio/mpeg" length="0"/>
      <guid>https://www.siriusxm.com</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 05:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1191</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[The Rest Is History] Greatest Paintings: Age of Enlightenment - Raeburn's Skating Minister</title>
      <description><![CDATA[How does Henry Raeburn’s Skating Minister represent both the Scottish Enlightenment and the Romantic movement? In what ways does subject Reverend Robert Walker’s personal history connect to the famous Dutch Golden Age? And, how did a controversy about the most reproduced image in Scotland  traumatise the Scottish national identity? 



In this new The Rest Is History Club series, Tom is joined by art critic and author Laura Cumming to discuss the histories behind famous paintings and put them in their historical contexts.



To hear the full episode, and all the other exclusive new episodes from Laura and Tom's paintings  series, coming out every Wednesday for the next four weeks, join The Rest is History Club at therestishistory.com



To hear these exclusive new episodes from Laura and Tom every Wednesday for the next four weeks, join The Rest is History Club at ⁠therestishistory.com⁠. 



NEXT WEEK… 
Jan 23rd: The Angelus - Jean-François Millet 



_______

Twitter:

@TheRestHistory

@holland_tom

@dcsandbrook

Video Editors: Jack Meek + Harry Swan

Social Producer: Harry Balden

Producers: Tabby Syrett & Aaliyah Akude

Executive Producer: Dom Johnson
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://pdst.fm/e/traffic.megaphone.fm/GLT4404067972.mp3?updated=1771345955" type="audio/mpeg" length="0"/>
      <guid>undefined</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>361</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>