<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
  <channel>
    <title>Tim's Evening Commute</title>
    <description>Smart, relaxing mix for the drive home.</description>
    <link>https://timlpratt.github.io/tim-commute-feed/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 22:20:24 GMT</pubDate>
    <itunes:author>TimBot</itunes:author>
    <itunes:image href="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/e/e4/Robot_icon.svg/1024px-Robot_icon.svg.png"/>
    <itunes:category text="Technology"/>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    
    <item>
      <title>[NPR News Now] NPR News: 02-21-2026 5PM EST</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NPR News: 02-21-2026 5PM EST
Learn more about sponsor message choices: podcastchoices.com/adchoices
NPR Privacy Policy]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://prfx.byspotify.com/e/play.podtrac.com/npr-500005/traffic.megaphone.fm/NPR7639268819.mp3?t=podcast&amp;e=nx-s1-20260221-1700-long&amp;p=500005&amp;d=280&amp;size=4480567" type="audio/mpeg" length="0"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c3c45c0-8fe3-4aa4-a55f-b66e9760e432</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 22:10:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>280</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Radiolab] Song of the Cerebellum</title>
      <description><![CDATA[One spring evening in 2024, a science journalist named Rachel Gross bombed at karaoke. The culprit was a bleed in a fist-sized clump of neurons tucked down in the back of her brain called the cerebellum. A couple weeks later, her doctors took a bit of it out, assuring her it was just helping her with motor coordination — she might be a bit clumsy for a while, but she’d still be herself. But afterwards, she didn't feel like herself. So she dove into the dusty basement of the brain (and brain science) to figure out why. What Rachel found was a burgeoning new frontier in neuroscience. We learn what singing Shakira on stage has to do with reaching for a cup of coffee — and how the surprising relationship between the two is making us rethink what we think about thinking.
Special thanks to Warzone Karaoke at Branded Saloon, Dr. Joanne Loewy and the Singing Together, Measure by Measure choir at the Louis Armstrong Center for Music and Medicine  (http://musicandmedicine.org/) at Mount Sinai Union Square, Dag Spicer and the Computer History Museum, Désirée Lie, Mark Gross, Daniel A. Gross, Brittany Aguilar, and, of course, Shakira.
EPISODE CREDITS: 
Reported by - Rachel Gross
Produced by - Sindhu Gnanasambandan
EPISODE CITATIONS:
Articles -

“Ignoring the cerebellum is hindering progress in neuroscience.” (https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39934082/), by Wang et al, 2025
“The cerebellum and cognition.” (https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29997061/), by Schmahmann JD. Neurosci Lett. 2019
“How did brains evolve?” (https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/11805823/), by Barton RA., Nature. 2002

Books - 

Vagina Obscura (https://www.rachelegross.com/book), by Rachel E. Gross

Sign up for our newsletter!! It includes short essays, recommendations, and details about other ways to interact with the show. Signup (https://radiolab.org/newsletter)!
Radiolab is supported by listeners like you. Support Radiolab by becoming a member of The Lab (https://members.radiolab.org/) today.
Follow our show on Instagram, Twitter and Facebook @radiolab, and share your thoughts with us by emailing radiolab@wnyc.org.
Leadership support for Radiolab’s science programming is provided by the Gordon and Betty Moore Foundation, Science Sandbox, a Simons Foundation Initiative, and the John Templeton Foundation. Foundational support for Radiolab was provided by the Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/mgln.ai/e/14/prfx.byspotify.com/e/dts.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/waaa.wnyc.org/758af4c0-a2c3-47ec-a2d8-05f41bfbde51/episodes/0a1600f7-8ae1-4031-b35d-be4e5f76044f/audio/128/default.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;awCollectionId=758af4c0-a2c3-47ec-a2d8-05f41bfbde51&amp;awEpisodeId=0a1600f7-8ae1-4031-b35d-be4e5f76044f&amp;feed=EmVW7VGp" type="audio/mpeg" length="0"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ee1494f-b12a-4422-a96a-83bc3406db76</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>2568</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Radiolab] Gray&apos;s Donation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Before he was even born, Sarah and Ross Gray knew that their son Thomas wouldn’t live long. But as they let go of him, they made a decision that reverberated through a world that they never bothered to think about. Years later, after a couple of awkward phone calls, they go on a quest and manage to meet the people and places for whom Thomas’ short life was an altogether different kind of gift. We originally made this story back in 2015, but we wanted to play it again because we love that it brings a view of science that is redemptive, tender, and unexpected.
Since we first released this episode, Sarah Gray wrote a book called A Life Everlasting (https://zpr.io/GVYisRaqe9d6), it’s a memoir about Thomas that dives into the world of organ donation and medical science. She’s also written a beautiful short story about shame called The Lacemaker Fairy Tale (https://zpr.io/Li5BMtfHmf92). And, right now she’s working on a script for a movie called Raincheck.
EPISODE CREDITS:
LATERAL CUTS -
The Cathedral (https://radiolab.org/podcast/cathedral)
The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks (https://radiolab.org/podcast/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks) 
Signup for our newsletter!! It includes short essays, recommendations, and details about other ways to interact with the show. Sign up (https://radiolab.org/newsletter)!
Radiolab is supported by listeners like you. Support Radiolab by becoming a member of The Lab (https://members.radiolab.org/) today.
Follow our show on Instagram, Twitter and Facebook @radiolab, and share your thoughts with us by emailing radiolab@wnyc.org.
Leadership support for Radiolab’s science programming is provided by the Simons Foundation and the John Templeton Foundation. Foundational support for Radiolab was provided by the Alfred P. Sloan Foundation.]]></description>
      <enclosure url="https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/mgln.ai/e/14/prfx.byspotify.com/e/dts.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/waaa.wnyc.org/758af4c0-a2c3-47ec-a2d8-05f41bfbde51/episodes/f9d86f2e-c86d-4b2b-92de-c6973efec724/audio/128/default.mp3?aid=rss_feed&amp;awCollectionId=758af4c0-a2c3-47ec-a2d8-05f41bfbde51&amp;awEpisodeId=f9d86f2e-c86d-4b2b-92de-c6973efec724&amp;feed=EmVW7VGp" type="audio/mpeg" length="0"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d1c8106-e86f-4c91-9a6a-bd32b19fdfe6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>1640</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>